And with that, And with that, we've
reached the last few minutes of this
program. You remember we started out in
week one vibe coding for fun and profit.
We built out, we went through all of the
idees, just introducing like agents,
cursor, copilot, codex, anti-gravity,
looking at all those plugins and and the
the idees themselves. Then our first
experience with YOLO. It feels like an
age away. Uh and then the commercial
MVP, that was cool. Then we moved into
claw code and open code and amp. It was
uh commands and checkpoints for the
first time and slash commands and Ralph
loops. And then we we things got more
serious. We we got to see that whole
workflow with Jura. That was cool. All
the way going through to to a git push
and built out that legal SAS platform.
And that finally took us to week three.
By this point I said that you were now
vibe engineering. You had gone from Vibe
coding to Vibe engineering as a
professional. And now this week was so
much fun. I knew it would be. We just
went crazy with first of all the idea of
multi-agents, which is kind of boring,
but then sub agents. I showed you hooks.
Sandboxing was a much more interesting
day than it might have sounded just from
the name sandboxing. Uh when we were
doing I think that for me anyway,
sprite.dev is the is the really really
great thing. But also running with with
claw code remotely. uh hopefully you
tried the the amperasan thing and also
using it from your mobile and then also
tagging Claude in a git issue. It's
fantastic. And then the large codebase
workflow day I didn't really do much
about work large codebase workflow
because I felt like we covered it
enough. Um but h yeah instead we we
spent a moment looking at some of the
other stuff. I I got to I think that
that Claude agent SDK is really
interesting, something that's definitely
worth more exploration if if if you
found that that something useful. And
then of course we looked at co-work and
and OpenClaw was just something to take
a nod at. It's uh it's all over the
news, at least for me at the moment. And
then the last couple of days have just
been so great looking at orchestrators,
of course, GSD uh Claude agent teams,
which which is definitely my favorite.
And then uh also the the craziness that
is Gas Town uh which was something we
did today. And then we finally very
quickly I showed you codeex sub agents
and then getting codeex to fix up uh the
massive API so we could have a real
finance workstation. Hopefully you've
recreated that yourself. That completed
our capstone project, project number
four. But I know what you're thinking.
It's we didn't do four projects. We did
six projects because we also did the
first person shooter on the first day
and we did the Space Invaders.
So, well, if they count as projects, so
that would make it six projects. Uh,
four commercial projects though. And
that means, of course, that you are no
longer a Vibe coder. You are no longer a
Vibe engineer. You are now an officially
an agentic engineer. I can fill in that
third strip. You have completed the
board. It's done. You're an agentic
engineer. Congratulations. And it
remains me to give you a huge thank you.
Thank you so much for surviving the
roller coaster, making it all the way to
the end. I promised you a roller
coaster, and I think I delivered. Uh so
remember, whether you like it or not,
something came with this package uh that
that is that is yours that you can't
avoid. It's like like a mandatory part
of it. And that is me. Uh I come with
it. you you you you you get me forever.
I I want you to to to reach out to me,
post on LinkedIn that you've completed
the course with something you learned,
some insight, something about it, and
and I will come in and amplify your
success. Make sure that others know
about it. I'd love it if you post some
of the projects you've built or some of
your thoughts on on what you like and
dislike about the different platforms
we've covered or the techniques. Uh as I
say, post the certificate. That's
something that is easy for me to
amplify. I would love to do so. Take a
look through some of my other courses if
that interests you. Uh I've got lots of
stuff to build you into being an AI
engineer and I have a program for people
who want to become proficient AI
engineers. I should also mention my
editor would kill me if I didn't mention
again that that uh to the extent that
you're willing to rate this course, that
is the main way that Udemy decides
whether or not to recommend it to
others. So if you found it useful, then
please do rate it. It makes an enormous
difference and I'm super grateful. But
more important than any of this, the
single most important thing for you, the
to-do that you must do is to build. It's
all about building. I hope that I have
equipped you with the missing manual to
this this alien tool that Andre Kapathy
spoke of. You now have the ability to
use this tool. Go use it. Go build some
amazing things. Build them. Share them
with me. I can't wait to see them. Thank
you so much again.